We're losing love with fear, a Thank
you
for
joining us.
Nessuno può sfuggire dal destino scelto.
Roman solo il risultato e
che voi sarete distrutti.
I don't need a body to be left behind me.
I can't breathe! I know! Hello!
I'm going to die with the wind
Yeah yeah yeah!
What the...
Why is it shit like Bucciarati?
Hey you!
Are you that damn sculptor
I keep hearing about?
Identify yourself now!
Really shouldn't screw around
when you're at gunpoint.
You're lucky my orders
want to kill you outright.
Although, now that I
see you're a stand user,
I can't say I'm not
tempted to just put one
between your eyes and get this over with.
Only thing is, I still gotta
find out who the hell you are.
We'll come back to the matter
of your girlfriend's fall later.
How do you know, Bucciarati,
and why did you follow me?
What are you...
Wait a minute, are you a cop?
That can't be the case,
they would never...
Let me tell you how this works.
The guy with the gun gets
to ask the questions.
That is the only rule.
So play along if you don't want to die.
And don't try anything funny, because I
am seriously not in the mood right now.
Every word that comes out of your
mouth better be 100 % true, or else...
Now then, I'll ask you
one question at a time.
Let's start with an easy one.
Are you a mafioso?
If you belong to a
syndicate, tell me which one.
Keep in mind, I can find
out later if I have to.
You've got it wrong.
I'm little more than a regular sculptor.
I'm hardly well known, but
I make enough to survive.
Explain how you became a stand user.
I'm sorry, but I don't know what
any of those words even mean.
If you're referring to this power,
it just sort of appeared
one day when I was a kid.
Was it the same for you?
Hey, quiet!
I got a lot more to ask.
Why the hell did you follow me
all the way from the restaurant?
And how does some randu like
you know who Bucciarati is?
Bucciarati?
Does that happen to be his name by chance?
Please, hurry!
Bring him to me now!
He entered the building with...
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You haven't answered any of my
questions, you son of a bitch!
I...
I'm afraid you're not going
to like what I have to say.
I can't control it.
The rock has its own independent will.
It's always been that
way, as far as I'm aware.
Unfortunately, there's nothing
I can do to rein it in.
However, you are not the person it wants.
Right now, the rock is
seeking out Bucciarati.
Oh, really?
Do I look stupid to you?
You better get serious about
this right freaking now,
unless you never want to
pick up a chisel ever again.
I know Bucciarati's
nowhere near this place.
So quit trying to fool me, because
I can hurt you a lot worse.
You're the only one fooling yourself.
Bucciarati is without a
doubt inside this building.
Once again, I'm begging
you to let me see him.
His life is in grave danger.
What did I say about lying to me?
Don't test my patience, you murderer.
I should end you for killing that girl.
What the hell are you
plotting now, asshole?
Which part of Don't Try Anything
Funny wasn't clear to you?
It's left.
It wants nothing from us.
What?
Allow me to share some art history.
The sculptor Michelangelo once said,
I approached the marble with chisel in
hand, But with no thought in my mind
For the stone already knows well The form
it is destined to take And to that end
My hands are tools Made simply to deliver
the medium But never shape it Laurie,
that's enough, you goddamn nerd!
I'm gonna need you to bring that
stupid rock back here right now!
Or I'll shoot you dead!
A sculpture's ultimate form is not
given Michelangelo would conject?
The sculptor's only job was to
unearth What fate had already created.
He could see Fate's design growing
clearer with each strike of his chisel.
Do you understand now?
I did not give the stone
Bucciarati's shape.
Neither did your bullets.
It was solely Fate's doing.
I'm guessing you saw the massive
chest wound and gush of blood.
Whether it will be in days or
months, none can really say.
But it is the way in which
Bucciarati will meet his end.
You and I are nothing
more than slaves to Fate.
That is the significance behind my power.
Prophecy stones.
This is the last warning I'll give you.
Bring that damn rock back now.
Because if your dumbass eats it,
then so does your little stand.
Do you get what I'm saying?
If he touches my prophecy stones,
I promise he'll be granted a
merciful release with no suffering.
So please, I only wish
to hear his last words.
Let me be by his side.
What the hell is this guy's deal?
Is he mocking me or something?
The bastard hasn't flinched
once this whole time!
Okay, fine.
If you seriously want me to spray the
place with your insides, then wish granted,
pal.
I got three whole bullets
while you just have one brain.
Let's take a look at what
fate buried in your mushy ass.
I know you're trying to do something
weird to Bucciarati, so stop playing dumb.
Call your freaking rock back!
Trust me, friend.
You really don't want to test
how much time you got left.
As I said, at this point there's
not a single thing more to be done.
Cut the bullshit act and bring
the rock back, you bastard!
The florist who sent you, his
legs were no good, were they?
He doesn't know it yet, but it's an
early symptom of some organ disease.
One he won't overcome.
At least not on his own.
Soon after the daughter passed,
her healthy organs were
preserved for transplantation
and will eventually save the man's life.
Poor girl found out about
her father's ailment
from the rock and learned
that in a few months,
she'd contract the disease too.
It was a revelation she accepted.
She chose death to save her father
and to avoid suffering later.
That's the reason why
she embraced the rock.
She was freed from the dark
fate awaiting her and granted
a merciful death which would
leave all her organs intact.
That's a pretty messed up way of saying
you killed an innocent girl, psycho!
What the...
It's a misfire!
Looks like that bullet was a dud.
Really?
Hey, that bullet was supposed to be
stupid number five's responsibility.
Get it?
It's not my time yet.
My death still hasn't found
its form in the stone.
If you really think I'm going
to shoot two blanks in a row,
then you've lost your tiny little mind.
What you felt just now
was destiny nudging you.
You've lost any real desire
to shoot me. Isn't that right?
You've got to be kidding me
with all this destiny bullshit.
There's no way any of that
made-up nonsense is real.
That bastard's just nuts.
Come on, come on, are you there, Fugo?
I got some news on our sculptor friend.
As it turns out, the guy's
a stand user. Wait, what?
Yeah, the weirdo won't shut up about
Bucciarati and Destiny and whatnot.
I can't make sense of anything
he's been babbling about.
I'd say the same about you.
Isn't Bucciarati there?
He got out of the car right after you and
headed straight to the apartment building.
I thought for sure he would've
caught up with you at this point.
Are you still there?
Give me a break!
What's going on?
Hey, Fugo, can you remember what the
number to Bucciarati's phone was?
It's really important that I
get to him right the hell now.
Whoa, hey, breathe.
The phone you're calling
is Bucciarati's, you moron.
Hey, Mista, you listening?
I'm counting on you guys.
Find Bucciarati, quick! Hello? You there?
All right, princess, nap time's over.
Now tell me how to stop this
damn rock from killing my friend!
Hey, I told you to wake up!
You answer me right freaking now!
Tell me exactly what I
gotta do to stop that
dumb pebble of yours
from reaching Bucciarati!
Come on, man, I'm begging you.
Please help me save my friend.
Look, I think I'm starting to
get all that stuff you said.
But you gotta tell me how
to turn this ship around.
Puchirati is not touching that rock.
I can't let that happen.
So please, what's the secret?
You gotta tell me!
I suggest you do not resist.
Acceptance is the easier path.
Still, if you're set on defying
the rock, there might be a way.
If you can destroy it or
reshape it somehow, then maybe.
We found him, mister!
We got eyes on Bucciarati!
A report came in from Number
One confirming it's him.
Bucciarati is somewhere
on the seventh floor.
Wait, I got it!
It's the stairwell!
He's climbing the stairs!
Oh, shit! No!
Not good, not good!
I see the rock!
It beat us to him!
Holy crap, what do we do?
He's gonna die!
Get it together, Number One!
Just focus on getting there
and tell him not to touch it!
It's no use!
Number One's bullet doesn't
have nearly enough juice
left in it to get him all
the way there in time!
Bucciarati!
Yee-haw!
Six bullets!
We made it!
That was close!
And it looks like we did to the thing!
I mean, it's cool that we've
got it crumbling and everything.
But I think we might have just
made stuff a whole lot worse!
Hey, Bullets, why don't you fill
me in on what's going on here?
Are we dealing with a stand?
And can any of you explain why
the hell it looks like that?
Oh no, Mujiraji!
Get away from it now!
Zipperman, go!
No!
Don't go, Zipperman!
If you touch it, you'll die!
Get down from there, quickly!
Mister, trust me, you're not gonna
wanna lay a finger on that rock.
One small tap and it's all over!
Explain yourself.
I'll do that as soon
as we get out of here!
Is that stone mass supposed to be a stand?
Please stop asking me all these questions
and run away for your life already!
Crap, it's slipping away again,
just like in the elevator.
Oh, damn it.
That thing could attack at any moment.
We'll need to find another way to get out.
This stairwell just turned
into a goddamn death trap.
Let's stay on our toes
and climb out of here.
Where is it I hate that slippery
little bastard where did it go
Mister what is it you've learned
Clever son of a bitch it's
right above you look out
Why does this rock bear that face
I just need to destroy the rock Or at
least try to change its shape somehow?
Mista!
If I smash it into the
pavement from this high?
That should be enough to
shatter its ass to bits!
I don't think so.
Oh no! Mista!
Holy shit.
He was telling the truth after all.
Everything went just as he said.
As long as you don't see your
own mug carved inside the stone,
you get to live on for at
least another day. Nice.
What the hell were you
doing in there, Mista?
You left the recorder in the
car after your tantrum, doofus.
Oh, hey.
It's you, Fugo.
So what on earth were you in the end?
Mista, I'd very much like the
explanation you promised me.
I mean, none of it matters anymore.
I...
I wouldn't know where to
begin, even. Oh, wait.
How about the old man's daughter?
It's the boyfriend, I'd say.
But technically, it also wasn't him.
Either way, he's not leaving the
hospital for at least a few months, so...
Unhelpfully vague as ever. Classic.
Is he a friend?
Or do we kick his ass?
Also, was it suicide?
Why don't you start from the beginning?
But see, that's the thing, though.
It's really hard to, you know,
piece this whole thing together
in a way that makes sense.
Look,
all you need to know is that I
destroyed the mean old rock stand,
so everything's peachy now.
Oh yeah, how's about you let me take
over the whole leaky eye Luca thing?
No thanks.
I've decided to do it myself.
Your reporting skills would slow things.
I believe I'll do just fine on my own.
Fugo, our florist friend
should get a detailed account.
Gather what you can from Mista.
Bucciarati, you know you
have my utmost respect.
But this guy here, he's a
puzzle even I can't solve.
Okay, don't hurt yourself.
We'll just have to use Abakio's...
So naive, do you really
believe this is the end?
If only you had accepted the stone's
mercy, all would be peaceful.
But you chose to remain enslaved to fate.
That which is carved in
stone cannot be changed.
Whoever you are, I hope you're ready.
A perilous journey of hardship awaits.
And for some of you, it
will be the last one.
I wonder, are all of you like him?
That young man flung
himself off a tall building,
all for a chance to save his friend.
Perhaps the path you are bound to walk
isn't one of meaningless suffering.
The adversity you'll endure may well
be the crucible of hope for another,
and perhaps it could be the
birth of a greater purpose.
Wishing for their safety will do nothing.
I can only hope that
they are sleeping slaves.
That's it.
Sleeping slaves will eventually awaken to
discover some meaning in their suffering.
Hey, what's the holdup?
Do you want me to heal Bucciarati?
Sure!
Why don't I just rub my gun on his wounds?
Dude, are you listening?
Whoa there.
You gotta watch your step.
Thanks, Mista.
Something really weird just popped up.
Trish?
Hey, Trish!
Where'd you go? Trish!
Hey, Giorno!
Where the hell did that girl go?
You startled me.
She's right there behind you. Look.
Guys, it's all right. I'm here.
The thing I tripped on
was next to the rock.
Check it out.
Don't go leaving me behind now.
Sorry I gave you all a fright.
I hope you'll still take me with you.
It's a long way for a lone turtle.
Why are you still here?
It's Mr.
Polnareff.
How are you alive?
If our souls were switched back to normal,
doesn't that mean yours should be...
Wait a minute, that's not right.
Wouldn't you...
and that?
My original body has perished.
But the moment my spirit
departed my flesh,
I made sure to hang on as tight
as I could to this turtle.
I'll remain bound to this key for a time.
I hope you won't mind little
old spectral me tagging along.
Hot damn, I'll admit I'm glad to
see you still kicking and stuff.
But the day's not over yet.
We still need to patch
out Bucciarati's injuries.
Wait, Bucciarati?
But I thought his soul was...
Whoa, what are you doing?
Oh crap, my bad.
I was just thinking maybe
you might have had a point.
My pits, they actually do smell like ass.
Can't believe I'm just
now learning about this.
Maybe I should put on cologne after all.
What?
Look, I might have exaggerated
a little bit earlier.
Everything happens so fast.
Right now, I don't think
you smell that bad.
In a super weird kind of way,
it actually feels nostalgic.
Oh my gosh, do you really mean that?
Yeah, but your fingers are freakish.
So then, what's your choice?
When those who've left us
place their wills in our hands,
it is our sacred duty to carry it forth.
It remains.
That's my choice.
Why don't you keep the
arrow in the turtle?
That'll do, Giorno.
A worthy decision to fulfill
your duty as a survivor.
Let us go to the Coliseum.
We have the mission,
they are the blessing,
but they dare to tell us
what's bad and what's good.
Stand up, join us, run,
I'll say this a lie,
we are the power, close to the
future, cause we are the fighters,
just fighting for a right.
Thank you.